如今你认为我写了成千上万首歌
By now you'd think I'd write a million songs
不过是心受伤后得到的才能
Gifts of a wounded heart
但是每次提到你 话太多了说不完
But when it comes to you, there's too much to say
而且我永远也不知从何开始
And I never know where to start
从那天起没人能替代你在我心中的位置
Since that day no one had taken your place
没人能补充你留下的空缺
No one can fill up the space you left behind
我问我自己 还能再爱吗
I ask myself, could I ever love again?
还是害怕再受一次类似的打击
And bear another beating of this kind?
又一次打击 又一次疼痛
Another strike, another ache
一个人能承受多少伤害
How much hurt can one take?
又一种害怕不能被我抹去
Another fear I cannot shake
不过是想搞清一颗心能承受多少伤害
Just how much hurt can one heart take?
现在你觉得我应该让你走
By now you think I would let you go
这样我晚上就不会再梦到你
That I'd stop dreaming of you at night
但我就是不能放下你
But I just can't stop thinking about
你怎能连打都不打一下就离开
How you walked away without a fight
你从未说过的那些话萦绕在我心头
The words you never said they haunt me
你所做的则锋利得像把刀
The one's you did were as sharp as a knife
我问我自己你有没有考虑过我的感受
I ask myself if you ever thought of me
当你慢慢回过神儿的时候
While you were slowly coming back to life
又一次打击 又一次疼痛
Another strike, another ache
一个人能承受多少伤害
How much hurt can one take?
天哪 又一个伤口
Another scar, for heaven's sake
一颗心能碎多少次
How many times can one heart break?
现在你觉得我会拿起电话
By now you'd think I'd pick up the phone
然后告诉你为啥我这么悲伤
And tell you I've been feeling so blue
但是每次提到你 话太多了说不完
But when it comes to you, there's too much to say
听你说得太多了
So much to be said by you